sportxe.com 2015-03-10

# Privacy Policy – SportXE

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to Gazer Media’s SportXE website and governs data collection and usage. By using the SportXE website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information:

Gazer Media may collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Gazer Media. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SportXE website.

### Use of your Personal Information:

Gazer Media collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Gazer Media may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Gazer Media. Gazer Media may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Gazer Media does not sell, rent or lease tis customer lists to third parties.

Gazer Media may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. Gazer Media may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SportXE, and they are required to maintain the confidentially of your information.

Gazer Media may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within SportXE, in order to determine what SportXE services are most popular. The data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within SportXE to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Gazer Media will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a)conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SportXE or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Gazer Media; and, (c)act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SportXE, or the public.

### Security of your Personal Information

Gazer Media secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

### Children under Thirteen

Gazer Media does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Gazer Media by contacting us here: Info@SportXE.com

Network Advertising Initiative opt-out Link <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

### Changes to the Statement

Gazer Media will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Gazer Media encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Gazer Media is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

Gazer Media welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Gazer Media has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us at [Info@SportXE.com](mailto:Info@SportXE.com)
